pondering on the balcony in a lazy afternoon
a cup of tea would be perfect now
walking along the path by the river, Changi
I will spend time with my lady friend, Dipti
at the local cafe
a bird is singing far away, I can hear
its unceasing melody
seems like an ask for something
why do I feel so lonely, so distracted
wildflowers are dancing
spreading their sweet scent
muted colors of the tired sun
are shades of yellow and orange
which bathe the hills of Khagrachori
in glorious beauty
Dipti walks to me and asks
have you seen such colors on a hill?
which holds the temple with such loving care
a bird is singing far away, I can hear
its unceasing melody
seems like an ask for something
why do I feel so lonely, so distracted
wildflowers are dancing
spreading their sweet scent
sipping the tea, she says,
here comes the season
lets cherish the flower celebration
and float our flowers together
on the waters of gracious Changi
speechless I, looked at her eye to eye
sincerely and softly I said to her
I like you a lot
why do I feel so lonely, so distracted
wildflowers are dancing
spreading their sweet scent
why do I feel so lonely, so distracted
wildflowers are dancing
spreading their sweet scent